[{"answer": "Originally a little bit.", "docId": "130819pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "Is that how you saw it?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "He didn't really kind of want to listen to anything.", "docId": "130819pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "But what do you think of the way the governor has gone about this generally?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130819pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "You know, Vivian on a good day will have, you know, maybe 10 seizures and those are myoclonic seizures.", "docId": "130819pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "I mean, Meghan, to put it into perspective for viewers, how many seizures can Vivian have in a day?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "Well, today it just went -- the conditional veto just got approved by the Senate in New Jersey.", "docId": "130819pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "Brian, the reality of the actions that Governor Christie took on Friday, when does that mean that you could actually use edible marijuana for Vivian legally in New Jersey?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130819pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "Are you tempted to take Vivian out of New Jersey and go somewhere like Colorado, for example, where it's all completely legal?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "Today she was pretty good.", "docId": "130819pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "And how is she at the moment, would you say, Brian?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "I did the first nappy, yes.", "docId": "130819pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "You did the first nappy change?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130819pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "He seemed very relaxed in that interview and happy to talk?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130819pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "You were comfortable there?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "He's extraordinarily appealing.", "docId": "130819pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "The new, mature dad Prince William?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "Well, (INAUDIBLE).", "docId": "130819pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "To me, it sounds utterly absurd but what do you think of it?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "It was a very unlikely picture in a way for Marissa Mayer because she's very sort of cool and almost Nordic in sort of an aloof beauty and charm and shyness.", "docId": "130819pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "Are you applauding Ms. Mayer for this?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "I'm good.", "docId": "130819pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "Abby, first of all, how are you?", "qSentId": 377}, {"answer": "ORGAN: Well, better than you last week.", "docId": "130819pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "What was going through my mind was, \"There's a bear attacking me.", "docId": "130819pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "Tell me what was going through your mind when this bear was coming towards you?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "Well, first I ran because I was terrified so I just started running and then it just took me down.", "docId": "130819pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "So what made you remember that?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "When the bear attacked me, it just clawed me and it was like growling and it -- yes, it was scary.", "docId": "130819pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "When the bear attacked you, what did it actually do to you?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "I was inside the house.", "docId": "130819pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "Where were you when this happened, Chris, and what was your reaction when you found out what was going on?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "No, I didn't.", "docId": "130819pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "Did you see the bear?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "Yes but it was almost one of the most terrifying.", "docId": "130819pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "I mean, Abby, when that bear left, that must have been one of the best moments of your life, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "She's had a few and she's lost a few, and she just didn't happen to have one at the time.", "docId": "130819pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "How's she going to call you?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "Yes, I'm on Facebook.", "docId": "130819pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "Are you on Facebook?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "It's been wonderful.", "docId": "130819pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "I mean, you must be loving this, aren't you?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "Oh, I'm sure they do.", "docId": "130819pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "I mean, does every prominent black star in America have similar stories to tell?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "Wow.", "docId": "130819pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "Lee, do you think that America is a more or less racist country since Barack Obama became president?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130819pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "Have you yourself suffered that kind of racism?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "I think that was the reason why I was attracted to the screenplay, because there's several trains of thought on what's the most affective way to go, but what has happened, I think with our youth today is there's been a real disconnect with the civil rights movement and the history of it.", "docId": "130819pmt", "aSentId": 529, "question": "Or should they adopt a more conciliatory way of going about dealing with racism?", "qSentId": 528}, {"answer": "Yes sir.", "docId": "130819pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "I think at the end of the day, it's a hard one because it is used, it has become a word that we use affectionately, in play.", "docId": "130819pmt", "aSentId": 588, "question": "What is your view about that debate?", "qSentId": 587}]